☆独家制作☆
喜马拉雅主播 & 微信公众号:
美国青少年英语
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
[screaming]
[screaming] shit! Shit!
‎妈的！
We're going down! We're going down!
‎我们要掉下去了！
Yeah, no shit, harrington!
‎是啊 净说屁话 哈林顿！
- Why don't these buttons work?!
- [Steve screams]
‎这个按钮为什么用不了？
[erica] press the button!
‎按按钮啊！
What do you think I'm doing?!
‎我按了啊！
Come on, press something!
Just press the button!
‎拜托 随便按点什么 快按按钮啊！
- [Screams]
- [erica] push it!
- [Crashing]
- [all grunting]
- [steve] oh!
- [Robin winces]
[steve] my groin.
‎妈的 我的腹股沟
It fell on my groin.
‎我摔到腹股沟了
Dustin! [strains]
‎达斯汀！
- [robin sighs]
- get this off of me!
‎把这玩意儿拿开
[steve] I can't move.
‎我动不了了
[grunts]
is everyone okay?
‎大家都没事吧
Yeah, I'm great, now that I know that
‎我好极了
‎现在我知道俄国人不会设计电梯了
russians can't design elevators!
I think we've clearly established
that those buttons don't work.
‎我觉得我们说得很清楚了
‎那些按钮没用
They're buttons. They
have to do something.
‎它们是按钮 肯定有一些用处吧
Yeah, if we had a keycard.
‎-是的 如果我们有钥匙卡的话
‎-什么？
- A what?
- It's an electronic lock.
‎这是个电子锁 和装货码头的门一样
Same as the loading dock door.
If we don't have a keycard,
‎如果没有钥匙卡 就没法操作
‎也就意味着...
- it won't operate, meaning...
- We're stuck in here.
‎-我们被困在这里了
‎-是
Yeah.
Just so you nerds are aware,
‎你们几个书呆子听好了
i'm supposed to be spending
the night at tina's,
‎我今晚本来要去蒂娜家过夜的
and tina always covers for me.
‎蒂娜总是会帮我打掩护
But if I'm not home for
uncle jack's party tomorrow
‎但是如果我明天
‎去不了杰克叔叔家的派对
and my mom finds out you
three are responsible,
‎我妈妈发现是你们三个人责任的话
she's gonna hunt you down, one
by one, and slit your throat.
‎她会把你们一个个找出来割喉
I don't care about tina!
‎蒂娜或者杰克叔叔的派对
‎和我没有任何关系
Or uncle jack's party!
Your mom's not gonna be able to find us
‎如果我们死在俄国人的电梯里
‎你妈妈也找不到我们的
if we're dead in a russian elevator!
[dustin] hey.
‎嘿
What if we climbed out?
‎我们能爬出去吗？
[dustin's grunts echo]
[steve exhales sharply]
what were you saying about climbing?
‎你刚说什么？爬出去？
[steve's voice echoes]
looks like somebody's home.
‎看起来有人在家
‎（山猫运输公司）
[door hinge creaking]
[low frequency pulsing]
did you hear that?
‎听到了吗？
[pulsing continues]
[hopper panting]
[floorboards creaking]
[pulsing continues]
[hopper gasps]
[hopper exhales sharply]
where's that coming from?
‎哪儿来的声音？
[pulsing intensifies]
[whispers] it's below us.
‎从下面来的
[hopper grunts]
[pulsing continues loudly]
[both breathing rapidly]
[suspenseful synth music playing]
[distant clanking]
[faint male voice]
[distant ratcheting noise]
[men speaking in russian]
hey, dipshits!
‎嘿 混蛋们
[metallic tool clatters]
hawkins pd. Hands in the air.
‎霍金斯警察局 举起手来
Don't make me say it again!
‎别逼我再说一遍
[speaking russian]
english.
‎英语
[hopper] you speak english?
‎会说英语吗？
[speaking russian]
I can't understand you!
‎我听不懂你在说什么
[speaking russian]
I can't understand you.
‎我听不懂
- [Speaking russian]
- no understand!
‎-不懂！
‎-霍珀！
- [Thudding footsteps]
- hopper!
[thudding continues]
[muffled groaning]
[muffled yelling]
[hopper] don't move!
‎不许动
Drop the gun.
‎放下枪
Drop it!
‎放下！
You understand what I'm saying, big guy?
‎听得懂我说话吗 大块头？
Drop the weapon.
‎-放下武器
‎-否则呢？
[in russian accent] or what?
You going to shoot?
‎你会开枪吗？
Good.
‎很好
[hopper] so you do understand
what I'm saying, huh?
‎所以你听得懂我说话 是吧？
And, yeah,
‎没错
you don't put that thing away,
i'm gonna blow some daylight
‎如果你不放下武器
‎我会给你厚厚的头盖骨
into that thick skull of yours.
‎开个窟窿 放点光进去
no.
‎不
You won't do that.
‎你不会这么做的
Why's that?
‎为什么？
Because you are policeman.
‎因为你是个警察
Policemen have rules.
‎警察有规矩的
Oh, yeah?
‎是吗？
[gun clicks]
wanna test that theory?
‎你想试验一下你的理论吗？
I'm gonna count to three.
‎我数到三
one,
‎一
two,
‎二
Three!
‎三！
[hopper grunts]
[yelling]
[fighting grunts]
[bullets ricocheting]
[joyce screams, grunts]
[hopper yells]
[fighting grunts]
[groans, coughs]
[grigori wails in pain]
[both panting]
[joyce] hopper!
‎霍珀！
- Oh, shit.
- [Grigori grunts]
‎妈的
[hopper] go!
‎快跑！
[gunfire]
[grunts]
[hopper] move, joyce!
‎乔伊斯‎ ‎快跑！
- [Joyce] oh, god.
- [Hopper] come on, smirnoff.
‎-哦 天啊
‎-来吧 斯米诺伏特加
You're coming with us!
‎你和我们一起走
- [Hopper] go, go, go!
- [Cocks assault rifle]
‎快走！
[joyce screams]
‎快点
[yells]
[hopper] let's go! Let's go!
‎我们走！
Move it, smirnoff! Move it!
run!
‎快跑！
[grunting]
joyce! Drive!
‎乔伊斯 开车！
[keys clatter]
- come on, joyce! Quit screwin' around!
- Are you kidding me?
‎快点 乔伊斯 别瞎磨蹭了！
[straining]
- shit!
- [Hopper] go!
‎他们的
Joyce, drive.
‎-乔伊斯 开车
‎-我在努力！
- I'm trying!
- Joyce, please, drive!
‎乔伊斯
Drive!
‎开车！
[yelling]
[hopper] get us outta here!
[engine roars]
[joyce screams]
[screams]
[both scream]
[hopper] oh, god!
‎老天啊！
[joyce] hang on!
[grunting]
[tires squealing]
[panting]
still think it was our government?
‎还觉得是我们政府弄的吗？
[panting]
[dramatic synth music playing]
‎NETFLIX 原创剧集
[theme music playing]
‎第五集：被夺者
[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
god, shut up!
‎老天 别吵了！
[ringing continues]
[groans]
- hello?
- Jonathan.
‎-喂
‎-乔纳森
Do you realize what time it is?
‎你知道现在几点吗？
Listen to me, okay?
‎听我说 好吗？
It's 6:00 a.m. And, uh,
‎现在是早上六点
‎我昨晚和费根那帮人玩到很晚 所以...
I had a late night with
fagin and the gang, so...
- I'm at the hospital with driscoll.
- What?
‎我在德里斯科尔所在的医院
She's been sedated for a few hours
‎-什么？
‎-她几个小时前打了镇静剂
and the doctors are still running tests.
‎-医生还在做检查
‎-请告诉我你在开玩笑
Nancy, please tell me you're joking.
It's not a joke. And,
yes, I know I'm insane
‎不是玩笑 是的 我知道我疯了
and irrational and out of touch,
but can you save your lecture,
‎不理智 与社会脱节
‎你先别忙着教育我了
because I really don't give
a shit right now. I just...
‎因为我现在根本不在乎这些 我只是...
I need you to put me on the phone
‎需要你叫你弟弟接个电话
with your brother.
- What?
- Jonathan...
‎-什么？
‎-乔纳森
Please.
‎拜托了
Uh...
He's not even here.
‎他都不在家
Where is he?
‎他在哪儿？他没事吧？
Is he safe?
Why wouldn't he be safe?
‎他为什么会有事？
Nancy?
‎南茜？
Why wouldn't he be safe?
‎他为什么会有事？
[steam hissing]
[hopper] son of a bitch.
‎狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
‎狗娘养的！
[hopper coughs]
okay, a magnet? Magnets?
‎好了 磁铁？
- Do you know "magnet"? Magnet?
- [Speaking russian] magnit.
‎你知道磁铁吗？
Yes, magnit.
‎-磁铁 是
‎-对了 磁铁 好
Okay, so, uh, magnit...
‎我冰箱上的 冰盒子上的磁铁
On my... My fridge,
my icebox, and then they...
They fell.
‎掉了下来
They demagnetized, stopped
working. Uh, do you understand?
‎被消磁了 不起作用了 明白吗？
da.
Okay, so is that because of the
machines that you're working on?
‎-好的 是你们在弄的机器导致的吗？
‎-机器
- Machina.
- Machina, machina, yes.
‎机器 是的
[imitates revving engine]
da, da, machina.
- Machina, machina!
- Yes, machina...
‎是的 没错
Vroom, vroom.
Oh, not... Not the car.
‎不是汽车
The machines at hess farm where...
‎海斯农场的机器
- Where we kidnapped you...
- Joyce, please!
‎-就是我们绑架你的地方...
‎-乔伊斯 拜托！
You're givin' me a
headache, both of you!
‎搞得我头都痛了
Hold on, please. One minute.
‎-你们俩都消停吧
‎-请等一下
[joyce] hey.
‎-嘿 我有进展
‎-进展
I am making progress.
- Progress.
- Yeah.
What have you learned, huh?
‎-是的
‎-你知道了什么？
You learned that smirnoff over there...
‎-你知道了那位斯米诺伏特加...
‎-阿列克谢
- [Joyce] alexei.
- Smirnoff is russian
‎斯米诺伏特加是俄国人
and works for starcourt,
‎为星庭工作
‎这两件事我们早就知道了
two things we already knew.
Thought we knew.
‎我们以为自己知道 但我们现在
‎确实知道了 因为我确认过了
But now we know-know,
because I've confirmed them.
You're welcome.
‎不用谢
Yeah? Why don't you confirm
whether this baby'll start, huh?
‎是吗？那你不如确认一下
‎这车还发不发动得了？
- [Hopper] keep it in park, please.
- Yeah, duh!
‎-拜托 挂在驻车档别动
‎-是 废话
You do... Do something useful.
‎你倒是做点有用的事啊
- You do something useful.
- [Sighs]
- [joyce scoffs]
- [groans]
[engine turns over]
[electric crackling]
[sighs]
it's not working.
‎发动不了
Try it again.
‎再试一次
[engine turns over]
shit.
‎该死
[engine sputters]
- [electric crackling]
- hey. Hey. [speaking russian]
‎嘿
stop, stop!
‎-停下
‎-闭嘴 斯米诺伏特加
Shut up, smirnoff!
[speaking russian rapidly]
aw, come on! D'you hear me?
‎拜托 没听到我说话吗？
I said shut your damn...
‎我叫你闭上该死的...
[high-pitched squealing]
shit!
‎妈的！
Oh, jesus.
‎哦 老天
[joyce gasps]
[hopper] whoa!
[gasps]
stop.
‎停下
[joyce] I thought this friend
of yours lived in illinois.
‎我以为你这个朋友住在伊利诺伊州
He's not really a friend.
He's more like an acquaintance.
‎不算朋友 只能算是熟人
Oh? Okay, well...
‎-好吧 那...
‎-嘿
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Keep up, keep up, keep up.
‎-跟上
‎-温柔一点
- Easy.
- [Insects buzzing]
okay, so this acquaintance...
‎所以这个熟人住在伊利诺伊州？
- Lives in illinois? Correct?
- [Hopper] yeah, yeah.
‎-对吗？
‎-是的
[joyce] so we're walking to illinois?
‎-所以我们要走到伊利诺伊州去？
‎-是的 我们走到伊利诺伊州去
Yeah, yeah, we're
gonna walk to illinois.
You know, I figure we'll get
there by, like, friday evening.
‎我估计我们周五晚上大概能走到
I hope that works for your
schedule. Jesus christ, joyce.
‎希望没影响你的时间安排 老天
- We're not walking to illinois, okay?
- Well, then what are we doing?
‎-我们不会走去伊利诺伊的
‎-好吧 那我们在干什么？
I don't know, okay?
‎我不知道 行吗？我会想出办法的
I will... I will figure something out.
Isn't there someone in indiana
who speaks russian that...
‎印第安纳州没人会说俄语吗...
You know what? I'm all ears, joyce.
‎你知道吗？我洗耳恭听 乔伊斯
I'm all ears.
‎我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears!
[joyce] I mean, fine.
‎好吧 成吧 我就那么一说
Just saying.
gah!
ugh!
[sighs]
[hopper] damn it.
I found him.
‎我找到他了
[max] where is he?
‎他在哪儿？
Woods.
‎树林里
- [Tv static hissing]
- woods?
‎-树林？
‎-他和威尔的妈妈在一起
He's with... Will's mom.
My... My mom?
‎我妈妈？
What are they doing?
‎他们在干什么？
Ill... Annoy.
‎伊犁挪移
They're going to ill-annoy.
‎他们要去伊犁挪移
- [Knocking on door]
- [karen] mike! Breakfast!
‎迈克！
Not now, mom!
‎-吃早饭了
‎-现在不行 妈妈！
Illinois? Illinois, like the state?
‎伊利诺伊？那个州？
The state of illinois?
‎伊利诺伊州吗？
[stammers] ill-annoy.
‎伊犁挪移
[tap stops]
[max] does it still hurt?
‎还疼吗？
Only when I talk.
‎只有说话的时候才会疼
Well, it's a good thing
you're not mike, then.
‎那幸好你不是迈克了
"blah, blah, blah, blah, blah."
And you'd be in constant pain.
‎否则会痛个不停的
[both chuckle]
[mike] something's not right.
‎情况不对劲
‎整个夏天霍珀都盯着我不肯放松
I can't get hopper off
my back all summer,
now all of a sudden, he's hiking
with will's mom to illinois?
‎现在他却突然和威尔的妈妈
‎去伊利诺伊州远足了？
And dustin's mia, too?
‎而且达斯汀也不见了？
I mean, this can't be a coincidence.
‎这肯定不是巧合
What does it matter?
‎有什么关系？
The bottom line is, they're not here.
‎关键在于 他们不在这里
- It's up to us.
- Up to us to do what exactly?
‎-都要靠我们了
‎-靠我们做什么？
Find billy and stop him.
‎找到比利 阻止他
Okay, yeah, that's a
really nice sentiment,
‎好吧 很好的观点
but even if el could find him again,
‎即使艾尔能再次找到他
‎这已经很困难了 然后怎么办？
and that's a pretty big if, then what?
We burn the shit out of him
‎我们用高温狠狠地烤他
‎确保他这次不会逃走
and make sure he doesn't
escape this time.
- Okay, then what?
- Then we win.
‎-好 然后呢？
‎-然后我们就赢了
No, see, that's the problem.
‎不 你瞧 这就是问题所在
We don't. We don't win.
‎我们不会赢
We got the mind flayer
out of will before
‎之前我们把夺心魔从威尔身上赶走
‎他直接就回来了
and he just came right back.
We don't just have to stop billy,
‎我们不仅需要阻止比利
‎我们要彻底阻止夺心魔才行
we have to stop the mind flayer.
- How in the hell do we do that?
- I don't know.
‎-那我们要怎么才能做到？
‎-我不知道
Maybe el does.
‎也许艾尔知道
What are they still doing in there?
‎她们还在里面干什么？
I don't know.
‎我不知道 女孩子都喜欢在厕所里玩
Girls just like hanging
out in bathrooms.
why?
‎为什么？
- I mean, I don't know.
- They're conspiring against me.
‎我不知道
‎-她们在预谋报复我
‎-你现在就担心这个？
That's what you're concerned about now?
It's not my main concern.
‎不是我主要担心的东西
‎是我次要担心的东西
- It's just a sub-concern.
- I thought it was already over.
‎我以为你们已经分手了
It's not over, okay?
We're just taking a break.
‎还没有分手 好吗？
‎我们只是暂时冷静一下
She said she dumped your ass.
‎她说她甩了你
- That doesn't sound like a break.
- [Max] it wasn't!
‎-听起来不像是冷静一下
‎-的确不是
You guys do realize
‎你们知道我们还是能听见
‎你们说的每一个字的吧？
we can still hear everything
you're saying, right?
[laughs]
[whispers] conspiring.
‎她们在预谋 正如我说的 她们在预谋
- I told you, they're conspiring.
- [Knock at door]
not now, mom!
‎现在不行 妈妈！
[nancy] mike, open the door.
‎迈克 开门
[dustin] code red, I repeat, code red.
Does anyone copy?
‎...红色警报 有人听见吗？
This is a code red,
I repeat, a code red.
‎红色警报 重复一遍 红色警报
This is a code red, I repeat,
a code red. Does anyone copy?
‎红色警报 重复一遍 红色警报
‎有人听见吗？
We are innocent children and we
are trapped under starcourt mall.
‎我们是无辜的儿童
‎被困在了星庭商场的地下
The red army has infiltrated
hawkins, and if we are found,
‎红军已经渗入了霍金斯 如果被发现
they will torture and kill us.
‎-我们会被折磨 会被杀死
‎-嘿
[steve] hey. [grunts]
gotta take it easy on that
thing. Gonna drain the battery.
‎你得留神一点用 会把电池耗光的
- The mall just opened.
- So?
‎-商场刚开门营业了
‎-所以呢？
So someone could be in range.
‎所以有人可能在对讲机射程内
What do you think, petey the
mall cop is gonna rappel down here
‎你以为呢？
‎你以为商场保安皮帝会绳降下来
and save the day?
‎救我们？
All right, why are
you such a cranky pants
‎好吧 你脾气怎么这么暴躁
after getting to spend
the night with robin?
‎你可是和罗宾共度了一个夜晚啊？
Shh! Jesus christ.
‎老天
Will you just give up on
your creepy dream already?
‎你能放弃你诡异的美梦了吗？
I heard you guys talking all night.
‎我听见你们整晚都在说话
We were trying to figure
out a way to open up the door
‎我们在想办法把门给打开
while you children were sleeping.
‎在你们俩孩子睡觉的时候
After eight hours,
‎八个小时后
we're still exactly nowhere, which is,
‎我们还是一无所获 所以...
you know, probably just a
little bit of the reason
‎这也许就是我感觉有点...
why I'm feeling just...
- A tad cranky.
- [Unzipping sound]
‎暴躁的原因
what are you doing?
‎你在干什么？
What does it look like I'm doing?
I'm taking a leak. Look away.
‎你觉得我在干什么？我在撒尿
‎转过身去
Look away!
‎转过去！
[steve's voice echoes]
[scoffs]
can you redirect your stream, please?
‎能拜托你换一个方向瞄准吗？
[robin's voice echoes]
ugh.
hey, hey! Be careful, careful, careful!
‎嘿 小心点！
We don't even know what that is.
‎我们都不知道这是什么
Exactly. It could be useful.
‎没错 可能会有用处
Useful how?
‎怎么个有用处？
We can survive down here
a long time without food,
‎没有食物我们可以在这里生存很久
but if the human body doesn't
get water, it will die.
‎但人体如果缺水 就会死
I hate to break it to you,
‎我真不想告诉你 但这不是水
but this is not water.
No, but it's a liquid,
‎没错 但这是液体啊
and if it comes down
to me drinking that shit
‎如果最后要选择喝这玩意儿还是渴死
or dying of thirst,
I drink.
‎我会选择喝这个
[scoffs]
[distant electronic whirring]
we've got company.
‎有人来了
[suspenseful synth music playing]
[beeping]
[elevator door thuds]
[indistinct female voice on pa]
[sniffing]
[in russian] you smell that?
‎闻到了吗？
[in russian] what?
‎什么？
Piss.
‎尿味
[sniffing]
[elevator door whirring]
[steve grunts]
let's go.
‎我们走
- Go. Go, go, go, go, go.
- [Erica] I'm going!
‎-快走
‎-我在走了！
- Henderson. Go, go.
- [Vial buckles]
‎亨德森 快走！
[robin] come on, steve, let's go!
[sizzling]
- jesus christ.
- [Erica] ooh!
‎老天
You still wanna drink that?
‎你还想喝吗？
Holy mother of god.
‎我的亲娘啊
Well...
‎这样
Hope you guys are in good shape.
‎希望你们体力还不错
Looking at you, roast beef.
‎说你呢 烤牛肉
Let's go, come on.
‎走吧 来吧
Why me?
‎为什么说我？
It was the same thing,
‎一模一样
the exact same thing that
happened to will last year.
‎和去年威尔的遭遇一模一样
And look at this. Look
at the body temperatures.
‎看看这个 看这个体温
‎（生命指征）
He likes it cold.
‎他喜欢寒冷
Okay, so this crazy old woman
who was eating fertilizer...
‎好 所以这个发疯吃化肥的老女人...
- Mrs. Driscoll.
- Right, yeah, Mrs. Driscoll.
‎-德里斯科尔夫人
‎-对 德里斯科尔夫人
- What time was this attack?
- Last night.
‎-什么时候被袭击的？
‎-昨晚
Right, but what time last night?
‎是 昨晚几点？
- Around 9:00.
- You waited all night to call?
‎-大约9点
‎-你等了一整晚才打电话？
I was waiting for the
doctors to run some tests.
‎我在等医生做检查
You weren't there?
‎你不在场？
Well, I'm here now, aren't i?
‎我现在来了 不是吗？
Hallelujah!
‎哈利路亚！
ooh.
Um, so, wha... What time
was your... Sauna test?
‎所以 你们的桑拿测试是几点？
[in unison] around 9:00.
‎大约9点
Well, that proves it.
That proves my theory.
‎那就证明了我的理论
She's flayed, just like billy.
‎她和比利一样被夺心了
- Flayed?
- The mind flayer. He flays people.
‎-夺心？
‎-夺心魔 他会夺人的心
Takes over their mind.
‎掌管他们的想法
Once they do that, they
basically become him.
‎一旦这么做了 他们就成了这个人
- If there are two flayed...
- We have to assume there are more.
‎-如果有两个人被夺心...
‎-我们必须假定还有更多人
Heather.
‎海瑟
Billy was doing something to her.
‎比利当时在对她做些什么
[heather whimpers echo]
she was scared.
‎她很害怕
She was screaming.
‎她在尖叫
- [Screams]
- bad screams.
‎不好的尖叫
- What's a good scream?
- Max said...
‎-好的尖叫是什么？
‎-麦克斯说...
- Doesn't matter.
- I'm sorry, I'm lost. Who is heather?
‎-不重要
‎-抱歉 我没跟上 海瑟是谁？
- She's a lifeguard at the pool.
- Heather holloway?
‎-她是泳池的一个救生员
‎-海瑟霍洛威？
[both] tom.
‎汤姆
[car doors shut]
seriously?
‎真的假的？
Welcome to my world.
‎欢迎来到我的世界
[mike scoffs]
seat belts.
‎系上安全带
[intense synth music playing]
[insects buzzing]
- oh, my god. Can you not walk so close?
- What?
‎-老天 你能别离我这么近吗？
‎-什么？
Can you not walk so
close to me? You stink.
‎你能别离我这么近吗？臭死了
[hopper laughs]
I get it, I get it. You're upset, right?
‎我懂的 你不开心了 对吧？
'cause i, uh... I blew up the car?
‎因为我把车给炸了？
Yeah, with me in it.
‎是啊 当时我还坐在车上
Well, I just want to remind
you of something, joyce.
‎我想提醒你一件事 乔伊斯
- I am not a mechanic.
- Yeah, clearly.
‎-我不是机械师
‎-对 很明显了
That's why you should've
listened to alexei.
‎所以你应该听阿列克谢的
Oh, right, yeah. Your
new boyfriend, right?
‎哦 是啊 你的新男友 对吧？
Yes. Every man I talk to from
now on has to be my boyfriend.
‎是啊 从现在起
‎和我说话的每个男人肯定都是我男友
Yeah, he reminds me a bit
of a russian scott clarke.
‎是啊
‎我觉得他有点像俄国版斯科特克拉克
Oh, here we go.
‎哦 又来了
Maybe you should go on a date.
‎也许你们应该去约个会
‎不知道 也许可以去恩佐餐厅？
I don't know, I'm
thinking, like, enzo's?
- Whoa.
- What?
‎-什么？
‎-他逃跑了
He's running.
[alexei whimpers, grunts]
you son of a bitch!
‎哦 狗娘养的！
- [Alexei mutters in russian]
- [hopper] hey! Smirnoff!
‎嘿 斯米诺伏特加！
Get back here!
‎嘿 快回来！
- [Alexei chuckles]
- hey! C'mere!
[grunting]
[hopper] hey, c'mere!
[speaking russian]
[all panting]
- [bell chimes]
- [light instrumental music playing]
[door bell jingles]
[grunts]
[man] you all gonna pay for those?
‎你们打算付钱吗？
[burps]
‎（伊利诺伊）
[register beeping]
so, what are you, some
kinda bounty hunter?
‎所以你算是个赏金猎人之类的角色？
I'm a cop.
‎我是个警察
I'm undercover.
‎卧底警察
[heavy metal playing on car stereo]
[music stops]
oh, hey, karen, it's joyce.
‎喂 凯伦 我是乔伊斯
Yeah, I... I'm just checking on will.
‎我只是想问问威尔的情况
At the movies?
‎去电影院了？
Just keep your mouth shut, all right?
‎闭上你的嘴 行吗？
[slurping loudly]
all right, all right,
hop in. Come on, get in.
‎好了 上车吧 来吧 上车
- Hey!
‎-嘿！
You "hey"! You "hey"!
‎叫你呢 嘿
This is a police emergency, all right?
‎警方紧急情况 明白吗？
I need to commandeer your vehicle.
‎我需要征用你的车
What?
‎什么？
As long as there's a... A...
‎只要有...
[hopper] what is your name, sir?
‎你叫什么 先生？
- Todd.
- Todd?
‎-陶德
‎-陶德？
- Yeah.
- Todd.
‎-是的
‎-陶德
- Todd.
- Todd...
‎-陶德
Listen to me.
‎听我说
That man in there,
‎车上这个人
I know he doesn't look it,
‎我知道他看起来可能不像
but he is one of the most
dangerous men in the world.
‎但他是全世界最危险的人之一
He's, uh...
‎他是...
- Murdered many children.
- What?
‎-谋杀了很多孩子
‎-什么？
Yeah, he's a true psychopath. I
tracked him over two state lines.
‎是 真正的神经病
‎我追了他两个州才追到的
[joyce] hey, what's going on?
‎嘿 怎么回事？
Ah, detective byers.
‎啊 拜尔斯探员
Uh...
This is todd.
‎这位是陶德
He's agreed to...
‎他已经同意将他的车借给我们
‎运送这位危险的犯罪分子
Lend us his vehicle to transport
our dangerous criminal.
Oh, yes, he... Very dangerous, uh,
‎-哦 是的 非常危险的伪造...犯
‎-是的
forger... Er.
Yeah. Uh, child murderer.
‎儿童谋杀犯
- Child murderer?
- We should really get going.
‎-儿童谋杀犯？
‎-我们得赶紧上路了
Hey, how do I get my car back?
‎嘿 我怎么把车要回来？
- You just call the station.
- What station?
‎-给警察局打电话就行
‎-哪个警察局？
- [Heavy metal resumes]
- ooh, I like the sound of that, todd!
‎这声音我很喜欢啊 陶德
Hey, what station?
‎嘿 哪个警察局？
You're doing the right thing!
‎你在做正确的事！
[tires squealing]
hey, what the... Hey!
‎嘿！什么...嘿！
Dude!
‎伙计！
[dustin] I mean, you have to admit,
as a feat of engineering alone,
‎你必须得承认
‎这本身就是个工程上的奇迹了
this is impressive.
‎令人惊讶
What are you talking about?
It's a total fire hazard.
‎你在说什么？这绝对是个火灾隐患
There's no stairs, there's no exit,
‎没有楼梯 没有出口
there's just an elevator that
drops you halfway to hell.
‎只有一个电梯 把你扔到地狱的一半
They're commies.
‎共产党嘛 他们不给人付工资
‎特喜欢走捷径的
You don't pay people, they cut corners.
To be fair to our russian comrades,
‎给俄国同志们说句公道话
I don't think this tunnel
was designed for walking.
‎我觉得这个隧道
‎设计出来不是用来走的
Think about it, they
developed the perfect system
‎仔细想想 他们设计了运送货物的
for transporting that cargo.
‎完美系统
It all comes into the
mall like any old delivery.
‎和其他货物一样进来
And then they load it up onto
those trucks and nobody's the wiser.
‎然后装上那些卡车 没人会怀疑
[steve] you think they
built this whole mall
‎你觉得他们建这整个商场
‎都是为了运输那个绿色的毒药吗？
so they could transport
that green poison?
I very seriously doubt it's
something as boring as poison.
‎我严重怀疑会是毒药这么无聊的东西
It's gotta be much more valuable,
like promethium or something.
‎肯定有价值得多 比如钷
What the hell is promethium?
‎钷是个什么鬼？
It's what victor
stone's dad used to make
‎维克多斯通的爸爸以前用它来做
‎半机械人仿生物以及神经机械学部件
cyborg's bionic and
cybernetic components.
You're all so nerdy, it
makes me physically ill.
‎你们都太书呆子了
‎搞得我身体都起厌恶反应了
No, no, no. No, don't
lump me in with them.
‎不 别把我和他们放在一起说
‎我不是书呆子 好吗？
I'm not a nerd, all right?
[robin] why so sensitive, harrington?
‎为什么这么敏感 哈林顿？
Afraid of losing cool points
to a ten-year-old child?
‎担心在一个十岁孩子面前
‎显得不那么酷？
No, I'm just saying I don't
know jack shit about prometheus.
‎不 我只是在说
‎我屁都不知道什么是普罗米修斯
[dustin] promethium.
‎钷
Prometheus is a greek mythological
figure, but whatever.
‎普罗米修斯是一个希腊神话人物
‎不管了 我想说的是
All I'm saying is,
it's probably being
used to make something.
‎它八成是用来建什么东西的
Or power something.
‎或是给什么东西提供能源的
- Like a nuclear weapon?
- Totally.
‎-像是核武器？
‎-绝对有可能
Walking towards a nuclear
weapon. That's great.
‎朝一个核武器走去 棒极了
- That'd be great.
- But if they're building something,
‎-真是棒
‎-但是如果他们的确是在建东西
why here?
‎为什么选在这里？
I mean, hawkins.
Seriously. Of all places.
‎霍金斯啊 真的 有那么多地方可以选
At the very best, we're a toilet
stop on your way to disneyland,
‎最好的情况下 我们这儿就是
‎你去迪士尼公园时路过的公厕
but maybe that's it.
Maybe it's our very...
‎也许就是这样 也许是我们...
- You think the russians know?
- About...
‎-你觉得俄国人知道了吗？
‎-关于...
- They could.
- So it's connected?
‎-可能会知道
‎-所以是有联系的？
- Maybe.
- How?
‎-也许吧
‎-为什么？
I don't know, but it's...
‎我不知道 但是...
[both] possible.
‎有可能
I'm sorry, is there something
you'd like to share with the class?
‎抱歉 你们俩有啥想分享的内容吗？
- [Static hissing]
- [man speaks russian on radio]
[both] walkie.
‎对讲机
[man continues in russian]
[in russian] "a trip
to china sounds nice."
‎去一趟中国听起来不错
If you tread lightly."
‎如果你小心应对的话
It's the code.
‎是那个代码
- Wherever that broadcast is coming from...
- It's close.
‎-不管那广播是从哪儿来的...
‎-都很接近了
And if there's one thing
we know about that signal...
‎我们对这个信号有一点可以确定
It can reach the surface.
‎可以抵达地面
Let's go.
‎我们走
[doorbell chimes]
[low frequency vibration]
tom?
‎汤姆？
heather?
‎海瑟？
Jesus, it's freezing.
‎老天 冻死了
[sniffs] do you guys smell that?
‎你们闻到了吗？
[all sniffing]
oh.
oh, god.
‎哦 老天
More chemicals.
‎更多的化学品
You think they're guzzling this shit?
‎你觉得他们喝了这些？
Yeah, either that or they just
went on a hell of a cleaning spree.
‎是的 要么是这样
‎要么是他们搞了一次疯狂大扫除
But last year, will
didn't eat chemicals.
‎去年威尔没有吃化学品吧
- Did you?
- No.
‎-你吃了吗？
‎-没有
This is something new.
‎这是新的东西
Mr. Clarke, fifth grade. Posit.
‎克拉克老师 五年级 假设
What happens when you
mix chemicals together?
‎把化学品混合在一起会发生什么？
[lucas and will] you
create a new substance.
‎创造出新的物质
- What if they're making something?
- [Max] in themselves?
‎-也许他们在创造新的物质？
‎-在自己体内？
I mean, come on, if you drink
this crap, it'll kill you.
‎拜托 喝下这些东西会没命的
Yeah, if you're human.
‎是啊 如果你是人类的话
[distant, faint pulsing]
[nancy] blood.
‎血迹
Yesterday,
‎昨天
tom had a bandage on his forehead.
‎汤姆额头上贴了创可贴
[suspenseful music playing]
he was attacked.
‎他被袭击了
Call 91... [grunts]
[thunderclap]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[door hinge creaks]
they must have tied them.
‎他们肯定被绑在这里
They must have taken them somewhere.
‎肯定被带去了某个地方
[thunderclap]
mrs. Driscoll.
‎德里斯科尔夫人
She kept saying...
‎她不停地说："我必须要回去"
"i have to go back."
[shrieks]
what if the flaying,
‎如果夺心
it's taking place somewhere else?
‎是在别的地方发生的呢？
There must be a place where
all this started, right?
‎肯定有一个开始的地方 对不对？
A source.
‎一个源头
Somewhere he didn't want me to see.
‎他不想要我看到的地方
[faint shrieking noise]
if we can find the source,
then maybe we can stop him.
‎如果能找到源头
‎也许我们就能阻止他
Or at least stop it from spreading
‎或者至少阻止它蔓延
‎或者不要再去搞那些化学品了
or doing whatever the hell
he's doing with those chemicals.
How do we find it?
‎我们要如何找到？
Mrs. Driscoll.
‎德里斯科尔夫人
If she wants to go back so
badly, why don't we let her?
‎如果她那么想回去
‎我们不如就让她回去？
[todd] ... This guy comes up to me,
‎这个家伙就走到我面前
i'm just pumping gas over here,
‎我在这边加着油呢
and he... Hey, whoa!
‎然后他就...喂！
Don't cross me right now!
‎现在可别惹我
- [Bell jingles]
- [light instrumental music playing]
[cash register beeping]
busy day?
‎今天很忙吧？
You could say that.
‎可以这么说
Some psycho stole that dude's car.
‎有个神经病偷了那家伙的车
What else?
‎还有呢？
- What?
- What else did he say?
‎-什么？
‎-你还看到了什么？
This psycho?
‎这个神经病
No offense, but I already went
over all this with the cops.
‎无意冒犯 我已经和警察说了一遍了
I'm not a cop.
‎我不是警察
Yeah, no shit, khrushchev.
‎是 不用说也知道 赫鲁晓夫
[grunts] oh, shit!
‎妈的！
[whimpers]
[grigori] don't look at them.
‎不要看他们
At me.
‎看我
Tell me
‎和我说说这个神经病
about this psycho.
[panting]
come on, let's go.
‎快点 我们走了 快走
Move it.
[doors slam]
I thought you said this
guy was a journalist.
‎我以为你说这个家伙是个记者
Yeah, he, uh... He was.
‎是 他曾经是
was?
‎曾经是？
[buzzer sounds]
[murray] look at the camera.
‎看着摄像头
The camera, above you to the right.
‎摄像头 在你右上方
Identify yourselves.
‎告诉我你们的身份
Jim hopper, joyce byers,
‎吉姆霍珀 乔伊斯拜尔斯
‎斯米诺伏特加
smirnoff.
- Alexei.
‎-阿列克谢
[murray] surname.
‎姓什么？
I don't know.
‎不知道
Family name!
‎姓什么？
Yeah, I know. I told...
I don't know, okay?
‎我懂的 我不知道 好吗？
Open the damn door!
‎把该死的门打开！
[joyce] hopper.
‎霍珀
It's all right. Don't worry.
‎没事的 别担心
He's a little bit eccentric, but...
‎他有一点点古怪 但是...
He's completely harmless.
‎完全无害
- [Shotgun cocks]
- [joyce gasps]
name.
‎名字
[in russian] get that out of my face,
‎把这玩意儿给移开
you bald american pig.
‎你个秃驴美国猪
[in russian] I may be bald,
‎我也许秃了
but you're the one in handcuffs,
‎但带着手铐的可是你 苏联人渣
soviet scum.
[in english] hi, jim.
‎嗨 吉姆
[big band music playing]
wait.
‎等一下
[device beeps and whines]
[electric crackling]
[device whirs]
[device beeps]
[loud beeping]
[in russian] watch it.
‎留神点！
[in russian] silence, scum.
‎安静 人渣
- How long is this gonna take, because I...
- No.
‎你还需要搞多久？因为我...
‎-不
- No, you do not get to question me.
- [Device beeps]
‎不 轮不到你质疑我
you have dragged an enemy
of the state into my home
‎你如此粗心大意地
‎拽了一个国家公敌到我家里
as carelessly as a child
drags in shit on his shoe.
‎就像粗心的孩子
‎把鞋子上的屎带回家一样
I will search him until I am satisfied.
‎我会搜查到我满意为止
[clears throat] jim. C'mere.
‎吉姆 我...
[joyce] just c'mere.
I need to talk to you.
‎-吉姆 我...
‎-怎么了？
[hopper] yeah, what?
- What?
- This is not gonna work.
‎-怎么了？
‎-这行不通的
- What do you mean?
- He's not eccentric, he's certifiable.
‎-什么意思？
‎-他不是古怪 他是正儿八经的疯子
[loud beeping]
- glass houses, joyce.
- What?
‎-玻璃房啊 乔伊斯
‎-什么？
- You know, pot calling the kettle black.
- Oh, come on.
‎-你懂的 五十步笑百步
‎-哦 拜托
- Excuse me!
- What?
‎-打扰
‎-干什么？
Do me a favor and move your
lovers' quarrel elsewhere.
‎行行好 小两口吵架去别处吵
- Oh, oh, this?
- No, no, no.
‎-哦 这个吗？不是小两口吵架 朋友
‎-不 绝对不是...
Not a lovers' quarrel, pal.
Spare me!
‎不要连累我
What is your problem?
‎你到底有什么毛病？
Please, stop talking!
‎拜托 闭嘴！
No! We have had a very long day.
‎不！我们今天非常艰辛了
We have been shot at, nearly blown up,
‎有人朝我们开枪 差点被炸死
walked god knows how many
miles in a hundred degree heat,
‎三十七度的高温走了不知道多少里路
stole a car,
‎偷了一辆车
all while being chased by
this gigantic... Psychopath,
‎同时还被一个巨型神经病追杀
all so we could bring him to you.
‎目的只是为了把他带到你这里来
Because somehow, you're the
closest person who speaks russian,
‎因为不知道为什么
‎你是距离最近的会说俄语的人
which I can't believe.
‎这一点真是难以置信
But that doesn't matter because,
unfortunately, we're here.
‎但这也不重要了
‎因为很不幸的是 我们来了
So, if you don't mind,
‎所以如果你不介意的话
put that thing away,
‎把那玩意儿拿走
stop behaving like a jackass,
and ask him what he's doing
‎别表现得像个浑球一样了
‎问他到底在做什么
that's making my magnets
fall off my damn fridge!
‎搞得我冰箱上该死的磁铁
‎全都掉下来了！
Please.
‎拜托
[device whines]
[big band music plays loudly]
[indistinct male voice on pa]
okay, clear.
‎好了 安全
Clear, come on, let's go.
‎安全 快来吧
[robin] okay, that was close.
‎好险
- [Dustin] too close.
- Relax.
‎-太险了
‎-放松
All right? Relax. Nobody saw...
‎好吗？放松 没人看见...
[suspenseful music playing]
[female voice speaking russian on pa]
[indistinct chatter]
[steve] shit.
‎妈的
Jesus!
‎老天！
- Red dawn.
- I saw it.
‎-《赤色黎明》
‎-我看见了
- First floor, northwest.
- Saw what?
‎-一楼西北角
‎-看见了什么？
The comms room.
‎机房
You saw the comms room?
‎你看到机房了？
Correct.
‎正确
- Are you sure?
- Positive. The door was open for a second,
‎-你确定吗？
‎-确定 门开了一秒钟
and I saw a bunch of lights
and machines and shit in there.
‎看到里面有很多灯光机器之类的
That could be a hundred
different things.
‎那可能是一百样其他东西
I'll take those odds.
‎我愿意打赌
[sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
[steve whispers] all right.
‎好了
We're gonna move fast,
we're gonna stay low.
‎我们快速行动 保持低位
- Okay?
- Okay.
‎-好吗？
‎-好的
[woman speaking russian]
[man speaking russian]
shh!
move it.
‎快走
[door panel beeps]
let's go.
‎我们走
Sh, sh. Come on.
[female voice speaking russian on radio]
[in russian] tread lightly!
‎小心应对
Tread lightly!
[in russian] who are you?
‎你们是谁？
Silver cat... Silver cat.
‎银色的猫
I don't understand.
‎我不明白
- China?
- [Man scoffs]
‎中国？
[yells]
- [man grunts]
- [steve groans]
[steve grunts]
- [man yells]
- [steve grunts]
[man groans]
[panting]
[dustin] dude!
‎老兄
You did it!
‎你做到了！
You won a fight!
‎你赢了一场打斗！
[steve] jeez...
[laughs softly]
[steve chuckles]
- what are you doing?
- Getting us our ticket out of here.
‎-你在干什么？
‎-拿我们出去的钥匙
You want to walk all the way back?
‎你想一路再走回去？
Well, we can hang out for a little
bit, relax, have a picnic maybe.
‎没事 我们可以玩一会儿 放松一下
‎也许再吃个野餐
Have a picnic? We came
here for the radio.
‎野餐？我们是为了收音机来的
[dustin] this plan is way better.
‎这个计划好多了
‎如果我早知道史蒂夫能拿下俄国人
If I knew steve could
knock out a russian,
that would've been our
plan in the first place.
‎一开始就会这么计划...
[low frequency pulsing]
[men speaking russian]
- ... But I guess you're...
- Guys.
‎-但我猜你...
‎-各位
There's something up there.
‎上面有情况
[steve] let's go.
‎我们走
[men speaking russian]
holy shit.
‎妈呀
[low frequency pulsing continues]
[breathing masks hissing]
[electric crackling]
[loud thrumming]
[cracking noise]
[loud shrieking sound]
[woman] no, that is not mean.
‎不 那才不刻薄
That is honest.
‎那是诚实的表现
She won't find out.
‎她不会发现的
See, you're the only
one who gon' tell...
‎瞧 只有你会...哇 打扰一下！
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Excuse me!
Where do you think you're going?
‎你们这是要去哪儿？
Oh, um...
I was just going to
visit my grandma again.
‎我只是想再去看望一下我外婆
And... And this...
‎这是...
This is my family.
‎我的家人
- Extended.
- I don't care who they are.
‎-大家庭
‎-我不管他们是谁
You know the rules.
Two visitors at a time.
‎你知道规矩的 一次只能去两个访客
- Yeah, but...
- Two!
‎-是的 但是...
‎-两个人
Girl, this child has lost her mind.
‎这孩子疯了
She brought a whole zoo in here.
‎把整个动物园都带来了
[elevator dings]
[light muzak playing]
you know,
‎你知道吗
those things that I said yesterday, I...
‎我昨天说的那些事 我...
I didn't mean them.
‎我不是真心的
- I know.
- I don't think you're like those assholes.
‎-我知道
‎-我觉得你和那些混蛋不一样
At all.
‎完全不一样
I never have. I...
‎从来都没那么想过 我...
- I was just...
- Angry?
‎-我只是...
‎-生气了？
Which I still don't get.
‎这一点我还是不明白
I mean, I was just completely, utterly,
‎我只是彻头彻尾地、完完全全地、
mortifyingly...
‎令人羞愧地
Wrong.
‎错了
Don't let that go to your head.
‎别往心里去
I won't.
‎我不会的
I just look forward to you
never doubting me again.
‎我只是很期待你再也不会怀疑我
[elevator dings]
[vending machine whirring]
oh, come on, you piece of shit!
‎拜托 你这狗屎！
[low frequency vibration]
thanks.
‎谢了
Dude, I think that was it.
‎老兄 我觉得刚刚就是了
That was what?
‎是什么？
The olive branch.
‎橄榄枝
The what?
‎什么东西？
Oh, my god.
‎哦 老天
You're hopeless.
‎你无药可救了
Okay,
‎好吧
[whispers] I'll distract max,
‎我去支开麦克斯
get you an opening.
‎给你创造一个机会
And then talk to her. All right?
‎然后和她聊一聊 好吗？
[candy wrappers crinkling]
[ominous music playing]
[door creaks open]
where is she?
‎她人呢？
I don't know.
‎不知道
- Are you sure this is the right room?
- Yeah.
‎-你确定是这个房间吗？
‎-确定
[electricity crackles]
[tom] she's gone home.
‎她回家了
We were hoping you might come back.
‎我们也寄希望于你们会回来
Whose blood is that?
‎那是谁的血？
Tom, whatever you've done, it's not you.
‎汤姆 不管你做了什么 都不是你的错
He's making you do this.
‎是他逼你做的
[jonathan grunts]
go!
‎快跑！
[nancy gasps]
owie.
‎好痛
Go, go, go!
‎快跑！
[both panting]
- [stairwell door shuts]
- run!
‎快来！
Yeah! [laughs]
‎耶！
- [max] got it, two in a row.
- [Lucas] that was good, that was good.
‎-成功 连续两次
‎-很棒
[max and lucas cheering]
[lucas speaks indistinctly]
‎-瞧见了吗？我很擅长抛
‎-我很擅长接 所以...
- [max] best three in a row now.
- Hey.
‎-三局两胜
‎-嘿
hi.
‎嗨
Does your species like m&m's?
‎你们的种族喜欢吃MM豆吗？
[gentle synth music playing]
I like the new look,
by the way. It's cool.
‎顺便说 我喜欢你的新扮相 很酷
Thanks.
‎谢谢
[both panting]
[jonathan] run!
‎接着跑！
[jonathan] this way, this way!
‎这边走
[both panting]
nancy!
‎南茜
- [Intercom buzzer sounds]
- hello? Hello?!
‎有人吗？
Here.
‎这边
[both panting]
it's ringing.
‎打通了
I don't care how good her pie is.
‎我才不在乎她做的派有多好吃
No, I don't want her in my damn house.
‎我才不想要她来我家
Come on, pick up!
‎拜托 快接电话啊！
Nancy?
‎南茜？
[nancy gasps]
- hi there.
- [Glass shattering]
‎你们好
[ringing tone]
[nancy gasps]
i'm here for you, nancy drew.
‎我是来找你的 南茜茱儿
[nancy whimpers]
[jonathan grunts, groans]
- no! [grunts]
- [glass shatters]
‎不！
[jonathan choking]
[jonathan grunts, groans]
[bruce snarls]
jonathan!
‎乔纳森！
[nancy yelps]
[panting]
- [breathing rapidly]
- [gasps]
- [nancy yells]
- [bruce groans]
[bruce groans]
[grunts]
- you bitch.
- [Jonathan] nancy!
‎-你个婊子
‎-南茜！
- [Jonathan] run!
- [Nancy whimpers]
‎快跑！
[grunts]
[panting]
help! Help!
‎救命！
Help!
Is anyone here?!
‎有人吗？
Nancy.
‎南茜
[bruce] nancy!
[nancy whimpers]
[straining grunts]
[grunts, coughs]
[echoing] where are you going?
‎你这是要去哪儿？
[panting]
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[tom inhales sharply]
[tom yells]
[grunts]
yoo-hoo.
‎哟呵
Nancy drew, where are you?
‎南茜茱儿 你在哪儿？
[jonathan groans]
[grunts, gasps]
[tom grunts]
nancy.
‎南茜
[grunting]
[tom panting menacingly]
[jonathan whimpers]
[bruce] marco...
‎马可
Marco...
‎-马克
‎-波罗！
[nancy] polo!
huh?
[grunts]
[moaning]
[groaning]
- [nancy yells]
- [tom groans]
[groaning]
[tom grunts]
go... To... Hell!
‎下地狱吧！
[choking]
[tom choking]
[panting]
[electrical droning]
[gasps]
[receptionist speaks indistinctly]
[ominous music playing]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[bruce continues grunting]
[chittering sound]
[groaning]
[squelching sound]
[babbling]
[bruce grunts faintly]
[panting]
[squelching sound]
[chittering and squelching]
[chittering sound continues]
[emergency lights clicking]
[low growling]
[shrieking]
[theme music playing]
‎字幕制作：美国青少年英语 （微信公众号&喜马拉雅主播）
[monkey screeching]